# Rafik **GHARBI** Full Stack Developer

I am a Full-Stack developer with almost 5 years of experience. My passion for development started with founding Microsoft club in my university where we made a lot of events and development camps that I was one of the participants/coach/coordinators, being part of it for almost 2 years was the best thing for me helping me take this path in life. Finally, I'm highly interested in self growth and spiritual life as well, this is more like my source of power along the day, moreover, my source of happiness and positivity.



### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

# November 2022

#### Today

#### Flutter Developer (full-time job), ZETA-Box, Sfax, Tunisia

- > Working in an Agile methodology.
- > Assuring Scrum framework as a Scrum Master.
- > Convert a desktop application into a web application using Flutter (FE only)
- ➤ Analyse the project and coordinate the needed tasks with the team.
- > Analyse and illustrate the project progress (KPIs) for keeping our progress update with the client.
- > Dive deeper into Flutter and redesign the dependencies to our design need.

Flutter | Dart | Git | Jira | Figma | Scrum Master | Project Management

# June 2023

# Today

### My Weekly Planner (part-time job), Personal Project, Sfax, Tunisia

Creating a multi-platform application (Android, iOS, Web, desktop, macos) for planning our daily task on weekly bases regarding our roles in life (e.g. Student, Father, Employee, ...) with a habit tracker and stats section to reflect on and adapt his plans accordingly.

Flutter Dart Hive Notion API Animation

### October 2022 April 2021

### Full Stack Developer (full-time job), FUTUREPROOF, Sfax, Tunisia

- > Working in an Agile methodology.
- > Familiarization with Jira, Git and Figma.
- > Being a part of great project where we meet directly with the customer and creating a solution together that facilitate the life of a lot of peoples.
- > Develop my design skills with Figma creating our UI before starting development.
- > Use Java Spring Boot, GraphQL, and other third-APIs for creating our back-end
- > Use Flutter to design our front-end, single code for Android and Web app
- > Being part of a self automated small team touching every aspect of the product (from brainstorming and creating the tasks, thought analysing and designing, to development and testing)

Flutter Dart Spring Boot SQL Git Jira Figma GraphQL Scrum

#### January 2020 December 2020

#### .Net Developer (full-time job), GSOFT, Ariana, Tunisia

- ➤ Working on Asp.net Core 3.1 projects to create client's website.
- ➤ Familiarization with Azure DevOps platform for tasks management.
- > Creating a flexible master template made up of different components for faster customer delivery, further more, creating our own NuGet for future use.
- > Working directly with the client for better clarification and client satisfaction.
- > Ensuring the cleaning and readability of our code.

Blazor framework .Net C# SQL HTML CSS JavaScript

### December 2018 July 2019

#### IT Engineer (Internship), HUAWEI TECH INVESTMENT, Tunis, Tunisia

- ➤ Familiarization with Huawei product Fusion-Sphere and Hardware equipment.
- > Changing and updating the Hardware when necessary.
- ➤ Autonomy on solving encountered issues within the platform upgrade.
- ➤ Working closely with R&D for solving complex issues.
- ➤ Handling the technical communication with customer.
- > Working on the acceptance tests with the customer.
- > Going in business trips for solving different issues with the Performance Report Surveillance server in customer network and upgrade it.

Fusion-Sphere Open-Stack Hardware Servers

#### February 2018 October 2018

### Creating a VR game (Graduation project), GALACTECH STUDIO, Tunis, Tunisia

Creating a puzzle game called Oudhna the lost village. A new concept of a virtual visit game on VR. (D) Oudhna the lost village - Game-Play ).

Unity VR 3D models 3ds Max C# Game Development Photoshop Visual effects particle systems Game Design

July 2017 August 2017

## Game development (Academic Internship), MEDITERRANEAN DEVELOPMENT INITIATIVE, Sfax, Tunisia

Learn game development and creating an android game. My choice was an endless runner game with the role of a programmer.

Android XML Java User Experience Firebase

February 2015

June 2015

## Creating a smart house (Graduation project), ELECTRONIC AND TECHNOLOGY SOLUTION, Sfax, Tunisia

Creating a prototype house based on a Raspberry Pi in which we could control all the equipment of this house by creating scenarios with a windows phone application.

Windows Phone Visual Studio C# Embedded systems Linux Scripting Python Electronics User Experience

September 2013

### Microsoft club foundation, CLUB ACTIVITIES (ISIMS), Sfax, Tunisia

June 2015

Technical and development manager. Organizing and participating in different activities. Coaching and ensuring the perfectness of organized DevCamp.

Microsoft Community Events Coding Devcamps Windows Phone WPF Azure

# **EDUCATION**

2015 - 2018 IT engineering degree, Private Higher School of Technologies and Engineering (TEK-UP)

2012 - 2015 Computer science bachelor degree, Higher Institute of Computer and Multimedia Sfax (ISIMS)

2011 - 2012 Physics and Chemistry field, Sfax Preparatory Engineering Institute

2010 - 2011 Scientific Baccalaureate (option: Computer Science)

# **S**KILLS

Programming Dart, Java, C#, C, SQL, PHP, JEE, HTML, Javascript, CSS, Swift

Frameworks Spring Boot, Flutter, Blazor, WPF, ASP, .Net

Database Oracle Database, Microsoft SQL Server, MySQL, FireBase, NoSQL

Development tools IntelliJ Idea, VSCode, Visual Studio, Android Studio, git

Operating System Windows, Linux, Android, iOS, Mac OS

> Raspberry Pi, Arduino Others

## A LANGUAGES

Forces



- > Problem Solving > Adaptability
- > Positive



☐ MTA 98-361 : Software Development Fundamental



#### INTEREST















Bodybuilding

Cinephile

Rafik Gharbi - CV